{
    "subject": "resource/Sabine_Peters",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "Sabine Peters",
    "human_readable": "The name of Sabine Peters is Sabine Peters.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9766481518745422,
            "question": "What is the name of Sabine Peters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9699113368988037,
            "question": "Is Sabine Peters known by another name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9666370749473572,
            "question": "What is the full name of Sabine Peters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9526816010475159,
            "question": "Who is Sabine Peters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8722023963928223,
            "question": "How can we refer to Sabine Peters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8078952431678772,
            "question": "Can you provide details about Sabine Peters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7269701361656189,
            "question": "What information do we have about Sabine Peters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6958949565887451,
            "question": "Is Sabine Peters a unique individual?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6947886347770691,
            "question": "Is there any additional information about Sabine Peters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5962329506874084,
            "question": "Do you have any other information related to Sabine Peters?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Sabine Peters is Sabine Peters.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6612_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any additional information about Sabine Peters?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6612_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Sabine Peters a unique individual?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6612_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What information do we have about Sabine Peters?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6612_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6612_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6612_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6612_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6612_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6612_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6612_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6612_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6612_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6612_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6612_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other queries!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that the name of Sabine Peters is indeed Sabine Peters. This can be inferred from all the documents provided, which consistently refer to the person by this name, without any variation or inconsistency."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe query \"The name of Sabine Peters is Sabine Peters\" is correct according to the documents provided, as all references use the names \"Sabine Peters\" consistently."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}